Guide to the Julia Driver Collection of Women in Photography
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Card Photographs and Other Photographic Materials, 1845-1940; Series II; 5.83
  - Photographic Materials
    - Fields, Margaret J. McGinley, Mrs. (born circa 1828), circa 1855-1890; (9 cartes-de-visite and 1 cabinet photograph) (Box 5, Folder 176)
      Also known as Mrs. William Fields
      Includes portraits of Alice Ford (born circa 1861), circa 1867, as well as Anna M. Smith (born circa 1854) and her sister, Clara W. Smith (born circa 1858), circa 1872
    - Findlow, Mary, Miss (circa 1835-1871), circa 1871; (3 cartes-de-visite) (Box 6, Folder 177)
      Active in Leamington, England, circa 1871
      Includes an occupational group portrait of bakers
    - Fish, Rhoda Ward, Mrs. (1816-1875), circa 1860; (2 cartes-de-visite) (Box 6, Folder 178)
    - Fitzgibbon, Marie Louisa Dennis, Mrs. (born circa 1836), circa 1876; (1 carte-de-visite and 7 cabinet photographs) (Box 6, Folder 179)
      Active in Saint Louis, Missouri, 1876-1884
      Also known as Mrs. John H. Fitzgibbon, Mrs. William Henry Clark, or Mrs. Fitzgibbon-Clark
      Includes portraits of Dr. Charles W. Stevens (born 1817), superintendent and physician to the St. Louis County Insane Asylum and coroner of Saint Louis County, and his grandchildren, Ida Sue Stevens (born 1873), Frank M. Stevens (born 1871), and Arthur Dillon Stevens (born 1868), 1879-1880
    - Flanagin, Hannah H., Miss (born 1838), circa 1870; (9 cartes-de-visite) (Box 6, Folder 180)
      Active in Woodstown and Pilesgrove, New Jersey, circa 1870-1890
      Also known as Miss H. H. Flanagin
    - Fleming, Jennie, Miss (born circa 1845), circa 1875; (4 cartes-de-visite) (Box 6, Folder 181)
      Active in Council Bluffs, Iowa, 1863-1884
    - Fleming, Sarah E. Jones, Mrs. (1859-1930), 1895-1900; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 6, Folder 182)
      Active in St. Charles, Iowa, 1895-1900
      Also known as Mrs. S. E. Fleming or Mrs. Jonathan L. Fleming
      Portrait of Mrs. C. V. Rundall with her grandson, Arthur Rundall Cole
    - Fletcher, Martha M. Crail, Mrs. (born 1829), 1859-1870; (4 cartes-de-visite) (Box 6, Folder 183)
      Active in Massillon, Ohio, 1859-1870
      Also known as Mrs. M. M. Fletcher, Mrs. A. Fletcher, or Mrs. Abel Fletcher
    - Fly, Mary "Mollie" Edith Goodrich, Mrs. (1947-1925), circa 1890; (1 card photograph) (Box 6, Folder 184)
      Active in Tombstone, Arizona, circa 1880-1912
      Also known as Mrs. Camillus Buck Sidney Buck
    - Folsom, Elizabeth, Mrs. (born circa 1848), circa 1888; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 6, Folder 185)
      Active in Danbury, Connecticut, 1884-1889
      Also known as Mrs. Joseph H. Folsom
    - Foote, Mary Millard, Mrs. (circa 1850-1890), circa 1885; (2 cartes-de-visite) (Box 6, Folder 186)
      Active in Lake Mills, Wisconsin, circa 1880-1890
      Also known as Mrs. F. Foote or Mrs. Frank Foote
    - Forssell, Amanda, circa 1890; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 6, Folder 187)
      Active in Sundsvall, Sweden, circa 1890
    - Foster & Wife, circa 1890; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 6, Folder 188)
      Active in Braymer, Missouri
      Also known as R. M. Foster & Wife
    - Foster, Eliza C., Miss, 1864-1866; (2 cartes-de-visite) (Box 6, Folder 189)
      Active in Ann Arbor, Michigan, 1864-1866
      Also known as Miss E. C. Foster or Eliza C. Foster & Co.
    - Frankel, Anna, circa 1881-1890; (2 cartes-de-visite) (Box 6, Folder 190)
      Active in Malmö, Sweden, circa 1881-1890
    - Frissell, Emily Curtis, Mrs. (born 1832), circa 1864-1885; (8 cartes-de-visite) (Box 6, Folder 191)
      Active in Fort Atkinson and Jefferson, Wisconsin, circa 1864-1885
      Also known as Mrs. E. C. Frissell or Mrs. Charles Frissell
    - From, Laura, circa 1900; (2 cartes-de-visite) (Box 6, Folder 192)
      Active in Toftlund, Denmark, circa 1900
    - Frush, Rosa T., Mrs. (born 1852), circa 1891; (2 cabinet photographs) (Box 6, Folder 193)
      Active in New Hampton, Iowa, circa 1891
      Also known as Mrs. R. T. Frush
    - Fry, Mrs., circa 1870; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 6, Folder 194)
      Active in Abingdon, England, circa 1870
      Exterior portrait of a child on a hobby horse
    - Fullerton, Jennie, Mrs. (born 1861), circa 1900; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 6, Folder 195)
      Active in Great Falls, Montana, as well as Langdon, North Dakota, circa 1892-1900
      Also known as Mrs. Robert Fullerton
    - Gage, M. D., Mrs., circa 1870; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 6, Folder 196)
      Active in Elko, Nevada, as well as San Francisco, California, circa 1870
    - Gagné, Ed., Madame, circa 1885-1895; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 6, Folder 197)
      Active in Montreal, Canada, circa 1885-1895
      Hand-colored portrait of a man
    - Galbreaith, Anna, Mrs., circa 1885; (2 cabinet photographs and 2 stereographs) (Box 6, Folder 198)
      Active in Manitou Springs, Colorado, circa 1870-1889
      Also known as Mrs. A. Galbraith, Mrs. H. Galbraith or Mrs. Harvey Galbraith
      Includes a view of Vulcan's Anvil in Monument Park, Colorado, and a portrait of a dog, as well as stereograph views of stalactites in the Horseshoe Tunnel of the Manitou Grand Caverns and of the Old Log Cabin Cascades in Cheyenne Cañon
    - Gallaher, Margaret Ferguson, Mrs. (1840-1901), circa 1870-1880; (2 cartes-de-visite) (Box 6, Folder 199)
      Active in Chippewa Falls, Wisconsin, circa 1870-1880
      Also known as Mrs. J. B. Gallaher or Mrs. Jerome B. Gallaher
    - Gantt, Mary J., Mrs. (born circa 1834), circa 1866-1870; (2 cartes-de-visite) (Box 6, Folder 200)
      Active in Lockport, New York, circa 1866-1870
      Also known as Mrs. M. J. Gantt or New Sun Light Gallery
    - Garland, Lizzie, Miss (born circa 1840), circa 1870-1880; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 6, Folder 201)
      Active in New Market, New Hampshire, circa 1870-1880
    - Garrity, Misses, circa 1880; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 6, Folder 202)
      Partnership between Sarah Garrity (born circa 1862) and Mary Garrity (born circa 1860)
      Active in Chicago, Illinois
      Also known as Le Grand
    - Garrity, Sally, Miss, 1887-1888; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 6, Folder 203)
      Active in Louisville, Kentucky, 1887-1888
      Also known as J. S. Brown & Co.
      Portrait of Lizzie Norman
    - Garrity, Sarah, Miss (born circa 1862), circa 1880; (3 cabinet photographs) (Box 6, Folder 204)
      Active in Chicago, Illinois, circa 1880
      Also known as Miss Garrity
      Also worked with her sister, Mary Garrity, as Misses Garrity
      Includes a portrait of Washington Hesling
    - Gay, Emily, Mrs. (born circa 1840), circa 1870-1880; (1 carte-de-visite, 3 cabinet photographs, and 1 piece of ephemera) (Box 6, Folder 205)
      Active in Fall River, Massachusetts, 1879-1900
      Also known as Mrs. E. F. Gay or Mrs. Edwin F. Gay
      Includes discrete portraits of a steamboat commander, chief engineer, and first pilot, as well as a bill from Gay to J. M. Lincoln for making views of Wareham, Massachusetts, January 4, 1886
    - Geiser, Julie, Madame (died 1874), circa 1865; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 6, Folder 206)
      Active in Algiers, Algeria, 1862-1874
      Also known as Madame Lucien-Jacob Geiser or Madame Julie Geiser-Pelot
      Exterior portrait of four Bedouin men and a boy with a lion
    - Gendron, Addie M., Miss, circa 1890; (2 cabinet photographs) (Box 6, Folder 207)
      Active in Westerley, Rhode Island, as well as Boston, Massachusetts, circa 1870-1897
      Includes a portrait of a young blind man
    - Gibson, Angeline, Mrs. (born circa 1842), circa 1870-1880; (3 cartes-de-visite) (Box 6, Folder 208)
      Active in Cedar Falls, Iowa, circa 1870-1880
      Also known as Mrs. A. Gibson or Mrs. Joseph Gibson
    - Gillett, Eliza Blood H., Mrs. (born circa 1814), circa 1853-1866; (22 cartes-de-visite) (Box 6, Folder 209)
      Active in Le Roy, New York, circa 1853-1866
      Also known as Mrs. E. H. Gillett, Mrs. G. C. Gillett, or Mrs. George Cooper Gillett
      Includes portraits of Emery Whitney (1791-1876) of Pavilion, New York, on August 10, 1865; Sophia Phelps (born circa 1817) of Pavilion, New York, circa 1866; 1st Lieutenant Edward S. Peck (born circa 1842) of Company B in the New York 100th Infantry Regiment, circa 1865; and Horace Chandler (born 1827), circa 1866
    - Gillett, Lucretia A., Miss (1820-1894), circa 1862-1870; (11 cartes-de-visite) (Box 6, Folder 210)
      Active in Saline, Michigan, circa 1862-1890
      Also known as Miss L. A. Gillett
    - Gilliland, Rebecca H. Greenlee, Mrs. (born 1827), circa 1870-1880; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 6, Folder 211)
      Active in Conneaut and Linesville, Pennsylvania, circa 1870-1880
      Also known as Mrs. R. H. Gilliland
    - Girod, Madame, circa 1865; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 6, Folder 212)
      Active in Paris, France, circa 1865
    - Glover, C. L., Mrs. (born circa 1828), 1864-1867; (2 cartes-de-visite and 1 tintype) (Box 6, Folder 213)
      Active in Syracuse, New York, 1864-1867
      Also known as Mrs. D. L. Glover
    - Godeus, Mary Anna Clifton, Mrs. (born 1849), circa 1870-1879; (3 cartes-de-visite and 1 card photograph) (Box 6, Folder 214)
      Active in San Francisco, California, 1866-1901
      Also known as Mrs. John D. Godeus
    - Goodlander Sisters, circa 1900; (9 cabinet photographs) (Box 6, Folder 215)
      Partnership of sisters Harriet Maud Goodlander (born 1879) and Maybelle Goodlander (born circa 1883)
      Active in Muncie, Indiana, circa 1900-1930
    - Goodwin, Rose A., Mrs. (born circa 1840), circa 1880; (2 cartes-de-visite) (Box 6, Folder 216)
      Active in Saint Johnsbury, Vermont, 1877-1880
      Also known as Mrs. R. A. Goodwin or Mrs. Frank Goodwin
    - Gore, Clara E., Mrs. (born 1855), circa 1880-1899; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 6, Folder 217)
      Active in Lacon, Illinois, circa 1880-1899
      Also known as Mrs. A. D. Gore or Mrs. Alonzo D. Gore
    - Gowe, Ada A., Mrs., 1895-1897; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 6, Folder 218)
      Active in Elyria, Ohio, 1895-1897
      Portrait of two men playing a clarinet and a violin
    - Graham, Ella, Miss (born circa 1870), circa 1895; (2 cabinet photographs) (Box 7, Folder 219)
      Active in Beloit, Kansas, circa 1895
    - Granger, Sarah, Miss (born circa 1840), circa 1870; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 7, Folder 220)
      Active in Brockport, New York, circa 1870
    - Granström, Hilma, circa 1900; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 7, Folder 221)
      Active in Kristinehamn, Sweden, circa 1900
      Portrait of Henny Hörnell with her signature on the recto
    - Grant, Isabelle van Buskirk, Mrs. (born 1853), circa 1890; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 7, Folder 222)
      Active in Lamar, Missouri, circa 1890
      Also known as Mrs. Belle Grant, Mrs. E. C. Grant, or Mrs. Ezra C. Grant
    - Graves, Mary Sophia Campbell, Mrs. (born 1814), circa 1864-1870; (14 cartes-de-visite) (Box 7, Folder 223)
      Active in Lockport, New York, circa 1864-1870
      Also known as Mrs. Edward Rufus Graves
    - Gray, Helen G., Miss (born circa 1843), circa 1870; (2 cartes-de-visite) (Box 7, Folder 224)
      Active in Blossvale, New York, circa 1870
      Includes a portrait of the photographer's brother, Frank Gray (born circa 1836)
    - Green, Arthur, Mrs., circa 1895; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 7, Folder 225)
      Active in Stockport, England, circa 1895
    - Green, Mia, (1870-1949), circa 1895; (2 cartes-de-visite) (Box 7, Folder 226)
      Active in Kemi, Finland, as well as Haparanda, Sweden, circa 1895
    - Gullbrantson, Ida, circa 1900; (7 cartes-de-visite) (Box 7, Folder 227)
      Active in Lund, Sweden, circa 1900
    - Gussone, Helene, circa 1880-1885; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 7, Folder 228)
      Active in Düsseldorf, Germany, circa 1880-1885
    - Gwynn, Mary Ward, Mrs. (born circa 1833-1836), circa 1881; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 7, Folder 229)
      Active in Madeley (Shropshire), England, circa 1881
      Also known as Mrs. Edwin Mabbett Gwynn
    - Hadlock, Arabella J., Miss (born 1844), circa 1865-1870; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 7, Folder 230)
      Active in Sterling, Illinois, circa 1865-1870
      Also known as Miss Belle J. Hadlock or Mrs. Marion F. Spaulsbury
    - Hagberg, Zelma, circa 1895; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 7, Folder 231)
      Active in Kristinehamn, Sweden, circa 1895
    - Hagen, Margit, circa 1890; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 7, Folder 232)
      Active in Denmark, circa 1890
    - Haley, Mary K. Walden, Mrs. (born circa 1830), circa 1860; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 7, Folder 233)
      Active in Metropolis, Illinois, circa 1860
      Also known as Mrs. M. K. Haley, Mrs. John Haley, or Mrs. Ernest Tarrant
    - Hall, Miss, circa 1870; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 7, Folder 234)
      Active in Fremont, Ohio, circa 1870
    - Hallström, Maria, circa 1900; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 7, Folder 235)
      Active in Gnesta, Vagnhärad, Järna, Södertälje, and Tumba, Sweden, circa 1890-1917
    - Hamlin, Fannie E., Miss (born circa 1835), circa 1870; (2 cartes-de-visite) (Box 7, Folder 236)
      Active in Lockhaven, Pennsylvania, 1870-1880
    - Haney, Ada, Miss (born 1879), circa 1900; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 7, Folder 237)
      Active in Wichita Falls, Texas, circa 1900
    - Hanson, Annetta, Miss, circa 1890; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 7, Folder 238)
      Active in Neenah, Wisconsin, 1887-1898
    - Hansson, Ellen, circa 1865-1880; (5 cartes-de-visite) (Box 7, Folder 239)
      Active in Göteborg, Sweden, circa 1865-1880
    - Hardy, Delia C., Mrs. (born circa 1815), circa 1860-1869; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 7, Folder 240)
      Active in Castile, New York, circa 1860-1869
      Also known as Mrs. S. P. Hardy or Mrs. Stephen P. Hardy
    - Harris, H., Mrs., circa 1885-1895; (2 cabinet photographs) (Box 7, Folder 241)
      Active in Blair, Auburn, Nebraska, circa 1885-1895
      Includes a portrait of a bride and groom
    - Harris, Rebecca J., Mrs. (1856-1941), circa 1900; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 7, Folder 242)
      Active in Clarksville, Arkansas, circa 1895-1910
      Also known as Mrs. Nathaniel Evan Harris
    - Harrison, Maggie, Mrs. (born circa 1852), circa 1880; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 7, Folder 243)
      Active in Galesburg, Illinois, circa 1880
      Also known as Mrs. T. Harrison or Mrs. Thomas Harrison
    - Harrison, Martha, Mrs. (born circa 1842), circa 1880-1890; (2 cartes-de-visite) (Box 7, Folder 244)
      Active in Kidderminster, England, circa 1865-1891
      Also known as Mrs. Edwin Harrison
    - Hart, Henrietta M., Miss (born circa 1829), circa 1863; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 7, Folder 245)
      Active in Plymouth, Michigan, circa 1863
      Also known as Miss H. M. Hart
    - Hart, Lovisa A., Miss (born circa 1830), circa 1870; (2 cartes-de-visite) (Box 7, Folder 246)
      Active in Whitewater, Wisconsin, circa 1870
      Also known as Miss L. A. Hart or Miss Louisa A. Hart
    - Harvey, A. A., Mrs., circa 1864-1865; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 7, Folder 247)
      Active in Logansport, Indiana, circa 1864-1865
    - Harvey, Julia Maud Westover, Mrs. (born 1849), 1875-1900; (1 cartes-de-visite, 1 cabinet photograph, and 1 tintype) (Box 7, Folder 248)
      Active in Maquoketa, Iowa, 1875-1900
      Also known as Mrs. H. P. Harvey, Mrs. Harry P. Harvey, or Levi Willard Schoonover
      Includes a portrait of Leonard Preston (born 1888), circa 1898
    - Haws, Jennie, Mrs. (born 1844), 1882-1888; (2 cartes-de-visite) (Box 7, Folder 249)
      Active in Decatur, Illinois, 1882-1888
      Also known as Mrs. J. Haws or Mrs. John H. Haws
      Includes a portrait of a bearded man wearing a dress
    - Haynes, Sarah Mary Narramore, Mrs. (born circa 1830), 1897 June 20; (1 stereograph) (Box 7, Folder 250)
      Active in Kingsbridge, England, circa 1861-circa 1891
      Also known as Mrs. James Haynes or Mrs. Joseph Ash
      View of the carriage and attendants of Queen Victoria in front of a crowd at St Paul's Cathedral during her Diamond Jubilee celebration
    - Heaton, M. E., Miss, 1893-1897; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 7, Folder 251)
      Active in Springfield, Ohio, 1893-1897
    - Hellyer, C. M., Mrs., circa 1875; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 7, Folder 252)
      Active in Mason, Michigan, circa 1875
    - Hermanson, Charlotte, 1905-1906; (3 cartes-de-visite) (Box 7, Folder 253)
      Active in Skara, Sweden, circa 1890-1909
    - Hertslet, Frances Sarah Church, Mrs. (1865-1948), circa 1905; (1 cabinet photograph and 1 card photograph) (Box 7, Folder 254)
      Active in Corning, Kansas, circa 1900-1920
      Also known as Mrs. Clement Townsend Hertslet
    - Hicks, Ellen Perry, Mrs. (born circa 1851), circa 1880-1890; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 7, Folder 255)
      Active in Sheffield, England, circa 1881-1891
      Also known as Mrs. T. S. Hicks or Mrs. Thomas S. Hicks
    - Hicks, Lydia A., Mrs. (born circa 1835), 1858-1870; (12 cartes-de-visite) (Box 7, Folder 256)
      Active in Brooklyn, New York, 1858-1870
      Also known as Mrs. L. A. Hicks or Mrs. Samuel Hicks
      Includes a portrait of a man wearing a United States Army frock coat with a sergeant rank, identified as Sergeant P. Leonard of the 173rd New York Volunteers
    - Hiester, Mary Frances "Fannie", Mrs. (1856-1933), circa 1890; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 7, Folder 257)
      Active in Lewisville, Texas, circa 1890
      Also known as Mrs. A. E. Hiester or Mrs. Albert E. Hiester
    - Higgins, Elizabeth, Mrs. (born circa 1828), circa 1870; (5 cartes-de-visite) (Box 7, Folder 258)
      Active in Stamford, England, 1856-1896
      Also known as Mrs. Henry A. Higgins
      Includes a portrait of a man identified as Major Dinas of the Royal Horse Artillery posed with a white terrier dog and holding the head of a fox
    - Hildebrandt, Miss, circa 1890; (6 cabinet photographs) (Box 7, Folder 259)
      Active in Marysville, Kansas, circa 1890
      Also known as Elite Gallery
      Consists of genre photographs of children playing character roles, including a hobo, as well as memorial photographs for a young girl.
    - Hill, Ann, Mrs. (born circa 1847), circa 1881; (3 cartes-de-visite) (Box 7, Folder 260)
      Active in Wolverhampton, England, circa 1881
      Also known as Mrs. Edward Hill
      Includes a portrait that probably depicts George Steward (born circa 1857) and his wife, Alice Steward (born circa 1851)
    - Hill, Eugenia, 1887-1890; (2 cabinet photographs) (Box 7, Folder 261)
      Partner with Milton Anthony
      Active in Longview, Texas, 1887-1892
      Also known as Anthony & Hill
    - Hinman, Julia Hunting, Mrs. (born circa 1830), circa 1860; (7 cartes-de-visite) (Box 7, Folder 262)
      Active in Holliston, Massachusetts, circa 1860
      Also known as Mrs. Hinman or Mrs. Lucieus S. Hinman
    - Hitchcock, Jeannette Blodgett, Mrs. (born 1838), circa 1865-1880; (30 cartes-de-visite and 1 cabinet photograph) (Box 8, Folder 263)
      Active in Canton, New York, circa 1865-1880
      Also known as Mrs. John Hitchcock
      Includes a portrait of Diadamie Ray (born circa 1807) from Russell, New York, circa 1865
    - Hoare, Susan, Mrs., circa 1898; (3 cartes-de-visite and 3 cabinet photographs) (Box 8, Folder 264)
      Active in Tahiti, circa 1898-1900
      Also known as Mrs. Charles Burton Hoare
      Includes a view of a tree-lined street and seated men with an inscription on the verso in Japanese, which translates "Present-day Tahiti," as well as a copy photograph of a drawing that depicts a tattooed Polynesian man.
    - Hogan, Rowena M., Mrs. (1868-1947), circa 1900; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 8, Folder 265)
      Active in The Dalles and Bend, Oregon, circa 1900-1930
      Also known as Mrs. J. J. Hogan or Mrs. James J. Hogan
    - Hohenshelt, Mrs., circa 1885; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 8, Folder 266)
      Probably active in the United States of America, circa 1885
    - Holcomb, Mrs., circa 1880; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 8, Folder 267)
      Active in Waverly, Kansas, circa 1880
    - Holmberg, Amanda, circa 1885; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 8, Folder 268)
      Active in Eksjö, Sweden, circa 1885
    - Holmes, Eleanor, Mrs. (born circa 1862), circa 1895; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 8, Folder 269)
      Active in Lytham, England, circa 1890-1901
      Also known as Mrs. James Holmes
    - Holmlund, Ida, Miss (born circa 1876), circa 1895; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 8, Folder 270)
      Active in Washburn, Wisconsin, circa 1895
    - Houser, Jennie Simanton, Mrs. (born circa 1843), 1875-1888; (6 cartes-de-visite) (Box 8, Folder 271)
      Active in Sterling, Illinois, 1875-1888
      Also known as Mrs. E. F. Houser or Mrs. Edward F. Houser
    - Howard, Ellen M., Mrs. (born circa 1841), circa 1870; (3 cartes-de-visite) (Box 8, Folder 272)
      Active in Alstead, New Hampshire, circa 1860-1880
      Also known as Mrs. E. M. Howard or Mrs. William Howard
    - Howe, M. E., Mrs., circa 1860-1869; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 8, Folder 273)
      Active in Jamestown, New York, circa 1860-1869
      Also known as Mrs. M. F. Howe
    - Hoyle, Lucy, Mrs., circa 1880; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 8, Folder 274)
      Active in Osborne, Kansas, circa 1880
    - Hoyt, Francis Bradshaw, Mrs. (born 1851), 1880; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 8, Folder 275)
      Active in Salt Lake City, Utah, 1880
      Also known as Mrs. Fannie Hoyt or Mrs. Hiram Hoyt
    - Hurley, Lottie C., Mrs. (born 1868), circa 1900; (3 card photographs) (Box 8, Folder 276)
      Active in Elmira, New York, circa 1900
      Also known as Mrs. L. Hurley, Mrs. S. L. Hurley, or Mrs. Samuel Lott Hurley
    - Hutchison, Mrs., 1898; (5 photographic prints) (Box 8, Folder 277)
      Active in Japan, circa 1898
      Includes a portrait presumably of her son, Donald Hutchison, dressed as Cupid, as well as views of Zushi in Kanagawa, Japan
    - Jacobsen, Anna, circa 1885; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 8, Folder 278)
      Active in Ollerup, Denmark, circa 1885
    - Jacobsson, Selma, circa 1890-1895; (2 cartes-de-visite) (Box 8, Folder 279)
      Active in Stockholm, Sweden, 1870-1900
    - James, A., Mrs., circa 1862-1864; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 8, Folder 280)
      Active in Lockport, New York, circa 1862-1864
    - James, Amy, Mrs., 1860-1865; (3 cartes-de-visite) (Box 8, Folder 281)
      Active in Belleville, Canada, 1860-1865
    - Jenik, Rosa, circa 1885; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 8, Folder 282)
      Active in Vienna, Austria, circa 1865-1900
      Also known as Rosa Jenik-Dörfler
    - Jenkins, Sarah M., Mrs., circa 1875; (1 carte-de-visite and 1 cabinet photograph) (Box 8, Folder 283)
      Active in Whitesville and Independence, New York, 1870-1900
      Also known as Mrs. O. A. Jenkins or Mrs. Orville A. Jenkins
    - Johansson, Lotten, circa 1890-1900; (2 cartes-de-visite) (Box 8, Folder 284)
      Active in Borlänge, Sweden, circa 1890-1900
      Consists of two discrete portraits of a bride and groom
    - Johnson, Adelaide, Miss (born 1848), circa 1870; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 8, Folder 285)
      Active in Adams, New York, circa 1870-1890
    - Johnson, Anna, circa 1895; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 8, Folder 286)
      Active in Stockholm, Sweden, circa 1890-1910
    - Johnson, Belle, Miss (1864-1945), 1894; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 8, Folder 287)
      Active in Monroe City, Missouri, 1895-1926
      Portrait of Howard Eugene Lear (1890-1915)
    - Johnston, Clara A., Mrs. (born circa 1841), circa 1865-1875; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 8, Folder 288)
      Active in Moberly, Missouri, circa 1865-1875
      Also known as Mrs. C. A. Johnston or Mrs. John Johnston
    - Jones, Caroline T. Barber, Mrs. (born 1829), circa 1870-1877; (2 cartes-de-visite) (Box 8, Folder 289)
      Active in Ames, Iowa, circa 1870-1877
      Also known as Mrs. G. W. Jones or Mrs. George William Jones